[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the film The Man with the Golden Gun?", "correct_answer": "Guy Hamilton", "incorrect_answers": ["John Hough", "Martin Campbell", "William Friedkin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What color does the traditional Ukrainian soup called Borscht have?", "correct_answer": "Deep red", "incorrect_answers": ["Bright yellow", "Deep green", "Intense blue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the last name of Italian brothers Carlo, Bindo, Alfieri, Ettore, and Ernesto who were all in the automobile business?", "correct_answer": "Maserati", "incorrect_answers": ["Romeo", "Peugeot", "Ferrari"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was the movie Return of the Magnificent Seven released?", "correct_answer": "1966", "incorrect_answers": ["1960", "1964", "1965"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Despite being the largest in the world, this island is sparsely populated, due to its unfavourable climate.", "correct_answer": "Greenland", "incorrect_answers": ["New Guinea", "Victoria Island", "Madagascar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Star Wars character delivered the line, Viceroy, we have captured the Queen.?", "correct_answer": "a droid", "incorrect_answers": ["stormtrooper", "a droideka", "a clone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the German ship that patrolled the lake in the 1951 movie, The African Queen?", "correct_answer": "Louisa", "incorrect_answers": ["Bismarck", "Von Braun", "Henrietta"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1994, what major hurricane broke the record for longest-lasting hurricane ever observed both in the Pacific Ocean and worldwide?", "correct_answer": "Hurricane John", "incorrect_answers": ["Hurricane Carrie", "Hurricane Ginger", "Hurricane Kyle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did American model and singer Mark Wahlberg advertise for Calvin Klein?", "correct_answer": "Underwear", "incorrect_answers": ["The Eternity Moment fragrance", "Coats", "Jeans"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If we are using  regular square graph papers, what do we call the point where the x-axis meets the y-axis?", "correct_answer": "the origin", "incorrect_answers": ["the abscissa", "the quadrant", "the ordinate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who won the 1958 Academy Award for Best Actress?", "correct_answer": "Susan Hayward", "incorrect_answers": ["Helen Hayes", "Althea Gibson", "Wendy Miller"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Larger parrot species have longer life spans than smaller ones. What is the average life span of a large parrot?", "correct_answer": "Up to 80 years", "incorrect_answers": ["20-25 years", "Up to 50 years", "14-15 years"]}]